(Raj:)Anyway, so I'm sorry
to waste your time.
(Raj:)And, uh... and good luck
with your screenplay.
(Claire:)Hang on.
(Claire:)We're both adults.
(Claire:)We can still get together
without it meaning anything.
(Raj:)Not me. Ever since
you admitted we had a vibe,
(Raj:)I've been planning our wedding.
(Claire:)Look, it's just coffee.
(Claire:)I'll ask you some questions
about science,
(Claire:)and if you propose,
I promise to say no.
(Raj:)Okay. That hurts a little,
but okay.
(Claire:)Great. I'll text you.
(Raj:)Bye.
(Penny:)All right.
(Raj:)So, uh, we're meeting
for coffee like two adults.
(Raj:)Everybody's happy. Easy peasy.
(Bernadette:)Are you gonna tell Emily?
(Raj:)Yeah, of course.
(Raj:)We have no secrets.
(Howard:)When are you gonna tell Emily?
He lied about the cream cheese!
He ate the whole thing!
I saw him!
(Amy:)Look, I know you think
I'm not right for Sheldon,
(Amy:)but trust me,
I'm his best shot.
(Amy:)You have no idea
how much I put up with!
(Meemaw:)I know more than you think I do.
(Amy:)Really? You know what it's like
to have date night ruined